MELVIN FRANCO

445 Central Ave A8
Orange NJ 07050
(973)558-0943
Melvinfv2010@hotmail.com

Profile

Hardworking and reliable general construction laborer with 10 years experience. Customer service experience in country clubs as server, cashier, and valet parking. Maintenance experience at schools and doctor's offices such as cleanings and repairs. Driver for Uber as well for deliveries.

Education

Criminal Justice Associates Degree 2009-2011

Experience

NJSB Construction

Painter/Laborer August 2021-present

Remodeling at commercial facilities such as schools, nursing homes, universities, etc. doing all types of work such as demolition, flooring, carpentry, painting, etc.

ISS Faculty Services

Maintenance September 2022-present

Maintenance of building facilities doing minor repairs, cleaning of all in and out of the building.

UBER DRIVER

Driver February 2021- present

Delivery driver for UBER doing passengers as well as food as an UberEats driver.

Skills

Adaptability

Forklift operator

Ability to Multitask

Floor scrubber operator

Knowledge of power tools and hand tools

Certifications

OSHA Certification

Languages

Spanish Fluent

References

Julio Palomino (973)715-0816

Nestor Tasayco (201)259-4497

Nenzly Brozey (201)874-2739